<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bing: Apple</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=Apple</link><description>Search results</description><image><url>http://www.bing.com:80/s/a/rsslogo.gif</url><title>Apple</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=Apple</link></image><copyright>Copyright © 2016 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright><item><title>Apple (India)</title><link>http://www.apple.com/in/</link><description>Apple leads the world in innovation with iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch, iOS, OS X, watchOS and more. Visit the site to learn, buy and get support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Inc. - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_Inc.</link><description>Apple Inc. is an American multinational technology company headquartered in Cupertino, California, that designs, develops, and sells consumer electronics, computer software, and online services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple - The latest on Apple - CNET</title><link>http://www.cnet.com/apple/</link><description>Check out the latest Apple news on CNET, featuring developments on the iPhone, iPad, Macbooks, OS X and much more.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 12:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Official Apple Support</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-in</link><description>Apple support is here to help. Learn more about popular topics and find resources that will help you with all of your Apple products.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 00:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>iPhone - Apple (IN)</title><link>http://www.apple.com/in/iphone/</link><description>Explore the world of iPhone. Check out iPhone 6s, iPhone 6 and iPhone SE. Visit the Apple site to learn, buy and get support.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple - Press Info - Apple Announces New iOS App Design and Development ...</title><link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2016/05/18Apple-Announces-New-iOS-App-Design-and-Development-Accelerator-in-Bengaluru.html</link><description>Apple Announces New iOS App Design and Development Accelerator in Bengaluru First-of-its-kind Center to Support Developers Creating Innovative Mobile Apps in India</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 08:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple (India) - Where to Buy</title><link>http://www.apple.com/in/buy/</link><description>Find out where to buy Apple products online, in a retail store or through a reseller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investor Relations - Apple</title><link>http://investor.apple.com/</link><description>The Investor Relations website contains information about Apple Inc. business for stockholders, potential investors, and financial analysts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 22:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Inc.: NASDAQ:AAPL quotes &amp; news - Google Finance</title><link>http://www.google.com/finance?cid=22144</link><description>Get detailed financial information on Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) including real-time stock quotes, historical charts &amp; financial news, all for free!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 03:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AAPL : Summary for Apple Inc. - Yahoo Finance</title><link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q?s=AAPL</link><description>View the basic AAPL stock chart on Yahoo Finance. Change the date range, chart type and compare Apple Inc. against other companies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 13:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>