<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bing: Einstein</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=Einstein</link><description>Search results</description><image><url>http://www.bing.com:80/s/a/rsslogo.gif</url><title>Einstein</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=Einstein</link></image><copyright>Copyright © 2016 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright><item><title>Albert Einstein - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albert_Einstein</link><description>Albert Einstein (/ ˈ aɪ n s t aɪ n /; German: [ˈalbɛɐ̯t ˈaɪnʃtaɪn] ; 14 March 1879 – 18 April 1955) was a German-born theoretical physicist.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Albert Einstein - Physicist, Scientist - Biography.com</title><link>http://www.biography.com/people/albert-einstein-9285408#!</link><description>Biography.com offers a glimpse into the life of Albert Einstein, the most influential physicist of the 20th century who developed the theory of relativity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Albert Einstein - Facts &amp; Summary - HISTORY.com</title><link>http://www.history.com/topics/albert-einstein</link><description>Find out more about the history of Albert Einstein, including videos, interesting articles, pictures, historical features and more. Get all the facts on HISTORY.com</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 05:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Albert Einstein - Biographical</title><link>http://www.nobelprize.org/nobel_prizes/physics/laureates/1921/einstein-bio.html</link><description>Albert Einstein - Biographical. Questions and Answers on Albert Einstein. Albert Einstein was born at Ulm, in Württemberg, Germany, on March 14, 1879.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 23:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Albert Einstein: Theories, Facts, IQ and Quotes - Space.com</title><link>http://www.space.com/15524-albert-einstein.html</link><description>Albert Einstein profoundly changed physics and ideas about space and time. Learn his theories, find facts and quotes from the man with an IQ of 160.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 09:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>About - Einstein Health</title><link>http://www.einstein.edu/about</link><description>Einstein Healthcare Network 5501 Old York Road Philadelphia, PA 19141 (215) 456-7890 (General Public) (215) 456-6730 (Media) Einstein Healthcare Network is a private, not-for-profit organization with several major facilities and many outpatient centers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 04:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Albert Einstein - Simple English Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://simple.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albert_Einstein</link><description>Albert Einstein (14 March 1879 – 18 April 1955) was a German-born theoretical physicist who developed the general theory of relativity, one of the two pillars of modern physics (alongside quantum mechanics).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 22:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Einstein: His Life and Universe: Walter Isaacson, Edward Herrmann ...</title><link>https://www.amazon.com/Einstein-Life-Universe-Walter-Isaacson/dp/1442348062</link><description>Einstein: His Life and Universe and over one million other books are available for Amazon Kindle. Learn more</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 23:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Official Licensing Site of Albert Einstein</title><link>http://einstein.biz/</link><description>Welcome to the Official Licensing Site of Albert Einstein. Learn more about Albert Einstein and contact us today for any commercial licensing inquiries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 19:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Albert Einstein - Wikiquote</title><link>https://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Albert_Einstein</link><description>Autoritätsdusel ist der größte Feind der Wahrheit. Unthinking respect for authority is the greatest enemy of truth. Letter to Jost Winteler (1901), quoted in The Private Lives of Albert Einstein by Roger Highfield and Paul Carter (1993), p. 79.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 16:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>