<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bing: sachin</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=sachin</link><description>Search results</description><image><url>http://www.bing.com:80/s/a/rsslogo.gif</url><title>sachin</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=sachin</link></image><copyright>Copyright © 2016 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright><item><title>Sachin Tendulkar - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sachin_Tendulkar</link><description>Sachin Ramesh Tendulkar (i / ˌ s ə tʃ ɪ n t ɛ n ˈ d uː l k ər /; born 24 April 1973) is a former Indian cricketer and captain, widely regarded as one of the greatest batsmen of all time. He took up cricket at the age of eleven, made his Test debut on 15 November 1989 against Pakistan in Karachi at the age of sixteen, and went on to represent Mumbai domestically and India internationally for close to twenty-four years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 02:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sachin Tendulkar - ESPN Cricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/india/content/player/35320.html</link><description>Sachin Tendulkar has been the most complete batsman of his time, the most prolific runmaker of all time, and arguably the biggest cricket icon the game has ever known.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 20:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sachin Tendulkar Profile - Cricbuzz | Cricbuzz.com</title><link>http://www.cricbuzz.com/profiles/25/sachin-tendulkar</link><description>View player profile of Sachin Tendulkar, live batting and bowling statistics for tests, odis, t20is, ipl and clt20 with career debut and last played matches scorecards on Cricbuzz</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tendulkar | He is a cricket hero</title><link>https://tendulkar.co.in/</link><description>About Me. Sachin Tendulkar. Mes cuml dia sed in lacus ut eniascet ingerto aliiqt es site amet eismod ictor ut ligulate ameti dapibus ticdu nt mtsen lusto dolor ltissim comes cuml dia sed inertio</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sachin Tendulkar Profile - in.com</title><link>http://www.in.com/sachin-tendulkar/profile-50.html</link><description>Sachin Ramesh Tendulkar is an Indian cricketer, and Member of Parliament. In ODIs, statistics confirm that Tendulkar is by far the most successful one-day batsman in history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 01:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welcome to Sachin.com</title><link>http://sachin.com/Sachin.com/Welcome.html</link><description>Welcome to Sachin.com, a collection of works, rants, raves, thoughts and other various collections from the mind of Sachin Kundra. You will find my various blogs here as well as my most prized posessions, my memories in the form of my collection of pics and movies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sachin Tendulkar | India Cricket | About Sachin Tendulkar Stats ...</title><link>http://sports.ndtv.com/cricket/players/14-sachin-tendulkar-playerprofile</link><description>Sachin Tendulkar cricket homepage at NDTVSports.com. Get Sachin Tendulkar cricket rankings info, Sachin Tendulkar records, individual records, Sachin Tendulkar photos, videos, stats, and about cricket in India</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 02:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bangalore - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bangalore</link><description>Bangalore / b æ ŋ ɡ ə ˈ l ɔː r /, officially known as Bengaluru ([ˈbeŋɡəɭuːɾu] ), is the capital of the Indian state of Karnataka. It has a population of about 8.42 million and a metropolitan population of about 8.52 million, making it the third most populous city and fifth most populous urban agglomeration in India. Located in southern India on the Deccan Plateau, at a height of over 900 m (3,000 ft) above sea level, Bangalore is known for its pleasant climate ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 17:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sachin Tendulkar - Times of India</title><link>http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/Sachin-Tendulkar</link><description>Latest Sachin Tendulkar News, Photos, Blogposts, Videos and Wallpapers. Explore Sachin Tendulkar profile at Times of India</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sachin (actor) - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sachin_(actor)</link><description>Sachin Pilgaonkar (Marathi: सचिन पिळगावकर; born 17 August 1957), often known by his first name Sachin, is an Indian film and television actor, director, singer, and producer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>