<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bing: AJAX</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=AJAX</link><description>Search results</description><image><url>http://www.bing.com:80/s/a/rsslogo.gif</url><title>AJAX</title><link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=AJAX</link></image><copyright>Copyright © 2016 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright><item><title>AJAX Tutorial - AJAX | W3Schools</title><link>http://www.w3schools.com/ajax/</link><description>AJAX is a developer's dream, because you can: Update a web page without reloading the page; Request data from a server - after the page has loaded</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 13:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajax (programming) - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ajax_%28programming%29</link><description>Ajax (also AJAX; / ˈ eɪ dʒ æ k s /; short for asynchronous JavaScript and XML) is a set of web development techniques using many web technologies on the client-side to create asynchronous Web applications.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 19:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is AJAX? - Tutorialspoint</title><link>http://www.tutorialspoint.com/ajax/what_is_ajax.htm</link><description>What is AJAX? - Learning AJAX Technology in simple and easy steps. A beginner's tutorial containing complete knowledge of AJAX, XMLHttpRequest, Response, ActiveXObject, Msxml2.XMLHTTP, Microsoft.XMLHTTP, Database Support, DOM Manipulation, Security Issues.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 01:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>jQuery.ajax() | jQuery API Documentation</title><link>https://api.jquery.com/jQuery.ajax/</link><description>A set of key/value pairs that configure the Ajax request. All settings are optional. A default can be set for any option with $.ajaxSetup(). See jQuery.ajax( settings ) below for a complete list of all settings</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AJAX Blog - AJAX Tutorial - Tutorials for Kanban, Erlang ...</title><link>http://www.tutorialspoint.com/ajax/</link><description>AJAX, is a web development technique for creating interactive web applications. If you know JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and XML, then you need to spend just one hour to start with AJAX. This tutorial will be useful for web developers who want learn how to create interactive webpages as well as improve</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 09:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tryit Editor v3.0</title><link>http://www.w3schools.com/Ajax/tryit.asp?filename=tryajax_first</link><description>Tryit Editor v3.0 ... Run » ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 01:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajax - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ajax</link><description>Mythology. Ajax (mythology), son of Telamon, ruler of Salamis and a hero in the Trojan War, also known as "Ajax the Great" Ajax the Lesser, son of Oileus, ruler of Locris and the leader of the Locrian contingent during the Trojan War</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 05:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajax Home Page - Ajax English</title><link>http://english.ajax.nl/Home.htm</link><description>Match selection Ajax for home game against Rostov . Video (5:11) Bosz: ‘Rostov no schoolboys’</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajaxdotcom Pvt Ltd</title><link>http://www.ajax.in/</link><description>Ajaxdotcom is in the Business Process Outsourcing industry since 1999. Starting out with Medical Transcription, over the years, it has expanded its range of service offerings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 07:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajax | jQuery API Documentation</title><link>https://api.jquery.com/category/ajax/</link><description>The jQuery library has a full suite of Ajax capabilities. The functions and methods therein allow us to load data from the server without a browser page refresh.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 13:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>